<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="69">
    <author>Bodzio528</author>
    <version>2.1.0.3</version>
    <title>
        <en>Crop Rotation</en>
        <de>Fruchtfolge</de>
        <fr>Rotation Des Cultures</fr>
        <pl>Płodozmian</pl>
        <cz>Střídání Plodin</cz>
        <it>Rotazione delle Colture</it>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[The Crop Rotation mod introduces incentive for growing different crops rather than planting potatoes over and over again.

Try yourself in reality, where nitrogen and lime are not the only nutrients that plants consume during their growth.

Gain up to 15% additional yield if done right.
Loose even more if you fail to take good care of the soil!

Key features:
- crop-specific return period to mitigate monoculture
- fallow support, up to two years (only with seasonal growth enabled)
- crop rotation info added to player HUD field information box
- detailed in-game help menu (with pictures!)
- crop rotation planner to visualize potential yield

Changelog 2.1.0.3:
- Crop Rotation planner added
- Precision Farming DLC is not required anymore
- small update to yield factors (up to 5% difference)
]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Der Fruchtfolge-Mod bietet Anreize für den Anbau verschiedener Pflanzen, anstatt immer wieder Kartoffeln anzubauen.

Versuche dich an der Realität, wo Stickstoff und Kalk nicht die einzigen Nährstoffe sind, die Pflanzen während ihres Wachstums verbrauchen.

Gewinne bis zu 15 % Mehrertrag, wenn du es richtig machst.
Verliere noch mehr, wenn du den Boden nicht gut pflegst!

Hauptmerkmale:
- kulturspezifische Anbaupausen zur Verhinderung von Monokulturen
- Brachlandunterstützung, bis zu zwei Jahre (nur bei aktiviertem saisonalem Wachstum)
- Informationen zur Fruchtfolge wurden der Feldinformationsbox des Spieler-HUD hinzugefügt
- Detailliertes Hilfemenü im Spiel (mit Bildern!)
- Fruchtfolgeplaner zur Visualisierung des potenziellen Ertrags

Changelog 2.1.0.3:
- Fruchtfolgeplaner hinzugefügt
- Precision Farming DLC wird nicht mehr benötigt
- kleines Update der Ertragsparameter (bis zu 5% Unterschied)
]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Le mod de rotation des cultures incite à cultiver différentes cultures plutôt que de planter des pommes de terre encore et encore.

Dans la réalité, l'azote et la chaux ne sont pas les seuls nutriments que les plantes consomment pendant leur croissance.

Gagnez jusqu'à 15% de rendement supplémentaire si vous prenez soin d'alterner correctement les cultures.
Perdez du rendement si vous ne prenez pas bien soin du sol !

Principales caractéristiques:
- intervalle avant replantage spécifique à la culture pour atténuer la monoculture
- promotion de la jachère pour redonner au sol le temps de reconstituer ses nutriments, jusqu'à deux ans (uniquement avec la croissance saisonnière activée)
- informations sur la rotation des cultures ajoutées dans la fenêtre d'information de la parcelle
- menu d'aide détaillé dans le jeu (avec images !)
- planificateur de rotation des cultures pour montrer le rendement potentiel

Changelog 2.1.0.3:
- Crop Rotation planner added
- Precision Farming DLC is not required anymore
- small update to yield factors (up to 5% difference)
]]></fr>
        <pl><![CDATA[Modyfikacja Płodozmian wprowadza zachętę do zmianowania upraw w miejsce hodowli monokulturowej.

Sprawdź, jak poradzisz sobie w sytuacji, gdzie azot i wapno same już nie wystarczają do zaspokojenia apetytu upraw.

Możesz zyskać dodatkowe 15% plonu, jeśli poprowadzisz zmianowanie poprawnie.
Możesz stracić więcej plonu, jeśli nie zadbasz o kondycję gleby!

Główne cechy:
- uprawy mają określone okresy powrotu na stanowisko: trzy lata, dwa lata lub coroczne
- możliwość zostawienia pola odłogiem, celem rewitalizacji gleby
- dane o zmianowaniu widoczne na panelu informacji o polu
- szczegółowy opis w menu pomocy (są obrazki!)
- planer płodozmianu pozwalający określić potencjalne plony

Changelog 2.1.0.3:
- Crop Rotation planner added
- Precision Farming DLC is not required anymore
- small update to yield factors (up to 5% difference)
]]></pl>
        <cz><![CDATA[Mod Crop Rotation nabádá uživatele ke střídání plodin namísto monokultur.

Vyzkoušejte si v realitě, kde dusík a vápno nejsou jediné živiny, které rostliny během svého růstu spotřebovávají.

Pokud jste udělali všechno správně, můžete získat až o 15% dodatečný výnos.
Naopak ztráta může být ještě větší, pokud se o půdu nebudete dobře starat!

Klíčové vlastnosti:
- návratové období specifické pro plodiny ke zmírnění monokultury
- podpora ladem, až na dva roky (pouze s povoleným sezónním růstem)
- informace o rotaci plodin byly přidány do informačního pole HUD hráče
- podrobné menu nápovědy ve hře (s obrázky!)
- plánovač střídání plodin pro vizualizaci potenciálního výnosu

Changelog 2.1.0.3:
- Crop Rotation planner added
- Precision Farming DLC is not required anymore
- small update to yield factors (up to 5% difference)
]]></cz>
        <it><![CDATA[La mod Rotazione delle Colture introduce incentivi per coltivare colture diverse piuttosto che piantare patate più e più volte.

Mettiti alla prova come nella realtà, dove l'azoto e la calce non sono gli unici nutrienti che le piante consumano durante la loro crescita.

Guadagna fino al 15% di rendimento in più se lo hai fatto bene.
Perdi ancora di più se non ti prendi cura del suolo!

Caratteristiche principali:
- periodo di ritorno specifico della coltura per mitigare la monocoltura
- sostegno all'incolto, fino a due anni (solo con crescita stagionale abilitata)
- informazioni sulla rotazione delle colture aggiunte alla casella delle informazioni sul campo dell'HUD del giocatore
- dettagliato menu di aiuto in gioco (con immagini!)
- pianificatore di rotazione delle colture per visualizzare la resa potenziale

Registro delle modifiche 2.1.0.3:
- Aggiunto il pianificatore di rotazione delle colture
- Il DLC Precision Farming non è più richiesto
- piccolo aggiornamento ai fattori di rendimento (differenza fino al 5%)
]]></it>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />
</modDesc>
